It's been a while.
好久不見了
When was the last time we met?
上次見面是什麼時候啊？
I think it was around the time you resigned as a prosecutor--
我記得是你辭掉檢察官的時候
Why did you want to see me today?
請問今天有何貴幹？
Now, now, no need to rush.
慢慢來，別那麼著急嘛
No, thank you.
不用了
Our relationship isn’t one for drinking sake
把酒言歡 沉浸在往日回憶不適合我們
and getting lost in memories together, is it?
我們不是那樣的關係吧？
I see.
這樣啊
I guess your admiration for me is a thing of the past now.
你尊敬我已經是過去的事了啊
How sad.
我好失落
Organizations are so terrifying.
組織這種東西真可怕
Even when you think
即使認真打造了一個
you've created one where everyone is straightened out and aligned,
讓所有人步調都一致的組織
there's always someone who steps out of line.
違反紀律的人還是一定會出現
I'm talking about Prosecutor Himeno.
我在說姬野檢座
Who else?
除了他還有誰呢？
I'm grateful to you.
我很感謝你
Thanks to you,
多虧了你
we were able to get rid of the rot in the organization.
才能清除組織的害蟲
I hope…
從今以後
you'll continue to be relentless.
也要請你繼續努力了，不必留情
That's my intention.
我正有此意
How promising.
那還真是可靠啊
By the way…
對了
I heard you're handling the case in Chiba.
你好像要負責千葉的事件吧？
Chief Kurata, huh?
跟倉田刑事部長有關的嗎？
Who are you talking about?
誰啊？他是哪位？
DAD: LET'S MEET AND TALK
（父親 我想跟你見面談談）
It's from my father.
是我父親傳來的
He wants to meet and talk to me.
他說想和我面對面談談
Will you?
你要去見他嗎？
Mr. Akizumi…
明墨律師他啊
is trying to use my relationship with my father.
打算利用我和父親的關係
Then I'll use that as well.
既然如此，我也要利用他
I heard you visited Yusaku Shimizu.
聽說你去見了志水裕策？
What about it?
那又怎樣？
It's moving.
很棒啊
An innocent person has been living in fear of death for 12 years.
無罪之人
And a hero of justice clears his false accusation…
你自認是替人平反冤案的正義英雄…
Is that your aim?
是不是？
He's guilty.
他有殺人
Yusaku Shimizu has admitted to his crime,
志水裕策承認了罪行
the court has convicted him of murder, and the case is closed.
法院也認定他是殺人犯
You agreed with the decision too, didn't you?
你也同意這個決定，不是嗎？
You remember, right?
你還記得吧？
After all,
畢竟就是你
you're the one who put him on death row…
讓志水成為死刑犯
As the prosecutor of justice!
當時你還是 為正義發聲的檢察官呢！
A friendly word of advice…
我就多管閒事，給你一些忠告吧
Don't expect everything to go your way.
你別以為所有事情都會如你所願
Mr. Akizumi,
明墨律師
you were aware that I was Kurata's daughter, right?
你早就知道我是倉田的女兒吧？
I was.
是啊
Then, please tell me.
那麼請告訴我
Six years ago,
六年前
you showed up in front of my father.
你出現在我父親面前
What?
什麼？
Answer me, Mr. Kurata.
請告訴我，倉田先生
You unlawfully covered that up, didn't you?
你是不是用不正當手段 掩蓋了那件事？
My father unlawfully covered something up.
我父親違法掩蓋了某些事情
I heard you accuse him of that.
你當時是那麼說的
It's…
那跟…
related to the Itoi family murders 12 years ago, isn't it?
12年前的糸井家滅門案有關吧？
Regarding that case,
關於那起事件
it appears Akamine is also interested.
赤峰好像也很在意呢
Huh?
什麼？
If you're going to tail someone, do it better.
你要跟蹤的話就該更敏捷
This time, you caught onto the possibility that the Chiba Police were colluding
這次你發現
with Attorney Uno and Ms. Eri Sendo behind the scenes.
可能私下串通，行違法之事
And so, you took over this case.
所以才奪取了辯護的工作
Because…
也是因為背後…
Isao Kurata, the Chief of Criminal Investigations, is behind it.
有倉田功刑事部長吧？
You invited me to this office
因為我是倉田的女兒
because I'm Kurata's daughter, right?
你才邀我進這間事務所 難道不是嗎？
I did.
沒錯
Please tell me.
請告訴我
What…
我父親…
did my father cover up?
到底掩蓋了什麼事？
Was he always engaging in such unlawful activities?
他從以前就在幹這種違法勾當？
Ms. Shinomiya…
紫之宮小姐
I believe you're aware that I'm using you.
我想你應該知道，我在利用你
What you want to know and what I want to know…
而你跟我想知道的事情
might lie in the same place.
都在同一條線上吧
If there's use in you,
如果你有利用價值
we might uncover something.
關於我們彼此都想知道的真相
The truth we both seek.
或許你能得知一些線索
We share a mutual interest.
我們彼此利害關係一致
So, let's work together.
就好好合作吧
Very well.
我了解了
What should I do?
我該做什麼？
Regarding this case of three consecutive instances of rape…
這個三起連續不同意性交事件
The Chiba Police decided
千葉縣警根據第三起事件的被害者 仙道繪里小姐的目擊證詞
of Ms. Eri Sendo, the third victim.
逮捕了來栖禮二先生
However, Ms. Eri Sendo's testimony raised several doubts.
但這位仙道繪里小姐的證詞 有很多可疑之處
Furthermore, it was found that she had been stalking Mr. Kurusu.
加上我們發現 她曾經是來栖先生的跟蹤狂
We've learned that the Chiba Police and Ms. Eri
千葉縣警和繪里小姐互相利用
might have been using each other to fabricate this incident.
捏造了事件的可能性很高
And Attorney Uno,
參與其中的是
who has a history of connection with the police, is also involved.
一直以來和警察關係深厚的宇野律師
He pretended to assist Mr. Kurusu,
他裝作要拯救來栖先生
only to make him confess and wrap everything up.
實則讓他自白以結束一切嗎？
Exactly.
沒錯
One lie connected three parties that shouldn't have been linked.
原本不可能搭上線的三人 因一個謊言而串聯在一起
And in a delicate balance at that.
還形成了一個很妙的平衡
So, if we can find evidence to expose their relationship…
那只要掌握可以揭發 這層關係的證據…
Such evidence doesn't exist.
沒有那種證據
The Chief of Criminal Investigations would never leave any evidence.
對方可是刑事部長
However,
不過呢
if their relationship only stands on a delicate balance…
如果他們是保持平衡 才能成立的關係…
Are you saying we should sever their connections?
只要打破關係就行？
Correct.
沒錯
First…
首先要…
We'll use Attorney Uno.
利用宇野律師
-Okay. Can you get in? -Yeah.
-好，可以乖乖坐好嗎？ -可以
Daddy! It's the man with the magic tricks!
爸爸！是那個魔術師的叔叔！
Akizumi…
明墨…
Yua is really cute, isn't she?
夢愛很可愛呢
I heard you lost your consulting position at that big trading company.
據說你和大型貿易公司的 顧問契約中止了
I imagine stepping down from Mr. Kurusu's case
你辭去幫來栖先生辯護的工作後
has pushed you into a tight spot.
日子很不好過吧？
And meeting with the police after that must have been awkward too.
肯定也沒臉面對警方
What are you getting at?
你想說什麼？
Ms. Eri Sendo's story…
與仙道繪里小姐的故事…
The police filled you in on that, right?
是警方告訴你的吧？
I don't know what you're on about.
我不知道你在說什麼
I don't know anything.
我什麼都不知情
If you want to expose my affair, go ahead.
你想揭發我外遇就去揭發吧
But if I did that, you'd really lose everything.
我那麼做的話，你真的會失去一切
You see, I have this feeling…
不過我覺得啊
that you aren't to blame for most of this.
其實你也沒那麼壞
You can play dumb and wiggle out of this.
你可以堅稱自己什麼都不知道
You took on Mr. Kurusu's case,
你接下來栖先生的辯護工作
and he just happened to confess.
而他恰巧自白了
That's all.
就只是這樣
What are you thinking of?
你在想什麼？
So,
那麼…
are we going to get Attorney Uno to blow the whistle on the invention?
你要讓宇野律師告發案件是捏造的？
No.
不
In order to upset this balance…
要破壞這個平衡
all we need is a little cooperation from him.
只需要他幫個小忙即可
What's going on? Hey!
你在拍什麼？喂！
He's one of my staff. He's capturing us together.
他是我的屬下
What are you planning?
你想要我怎麼做？
It's simple.
對你而言是很簡單的一件事
For your precious family,
為了重要的家人
you can't afford to lose your job, right?
你也不能辭去工作吧？
Next…
再來呢
we chip away at the weakest link.
從最脆弱的地方下手 讓他們的關係產生裂痕
Huh?
怎麼了嗎？
Sorry.
不好意思
I come here often for business.
我常來這裡工作
And I've always appreciated your welcoming smile.
你總是笑著迎接我 我一直覺得你人很好
I'm sorry I don't remember you.
不好意思，我不記得你了
Well,
沒關係
I do look rather plain.
因為我太不起眼了
No, not at all!
不，沒有這回事！
Um,
那個…
if you're up for it, how about some tea once you're off?
你不介意的話 下班後要不要一起喝個茶？
Really?
真的嗎？
Me?
我去嗎？
She's wary of me.
她對我有戒心
From now on, it's in your hands.
接下來的成功與否會取決於你
Handle it smoothly.
好好幹啊
So, Mr. Akamine, you're an attorney?
赤峰先生，你是律師啊？
Yes.
對
But I'm still kind of in training.
不過我還是實習生
I work under a tough boss, you see.
在有點難應付的律師底下工作
This here's Akizumi, my boss.
他就是我的上司明墨
He's a real piece of work and a real taskmaster.
他真的很麻煩，總是亂使喚人
We're working on the defense
我們…
for Mr. Reiji Kurusu.
負責替來栖禮二先生辯護
What do you want?
你要幹嘛？
You recognize this man, right?
你認識這個人吧？
I can't say.
不知道
This is Attorney Uno, the man initially handling Mr. Kurusu's defense.
他是一開始 幫來栖先生辯護的宇野律師
Aren't you curious about what they were discussing?
你不想知道他們在說些什麼嗎？
Here's the recording.
這是當時的錄音
The third incident.
關於第三起事件
Wasn't that story cooked up
那是警方和繪里小姐
by the police and Ms. Eri to fit their agenda?
為了讓自己獲利而捏造的吧？
And you knew about it when you took on the case.
你明知那點卻接下辯護工作
Isn't that right?
對吧？
"Don't be absurd."
別亂說話
"Do you have proof?"
你有證據嗎？
Right here.
請看這個
"That's…"
這是…
Will you keep making excuses?
你還想狡辯嗎？宇野律師
With this evidence,
都有這項證據了
I won't let you play ignorant to the fact that it was a setup.
可別再說不曉得這是假造事件了
"I had nothing to do with it!"
跟我毫無關係！
"Why should I care?"
我一概不知情
What on earth?
這是什麼？
You and the police invented the third incident.
第三起事件是你和警方聯手捏造的
We've got proof.
我們已經掌握了證據
What's the evidence?
是什麼證據？
We can't tell you that.
那可不能告訴你
I really am a victim.
我真的有受害
I'm leaving.
我要走了
Lastly,
在最後我可以談談你的未來嗎？
What?
什麼？
In upcoming trials,
我們今後會在法庭上
we'll bring forth evidence of your dishonesty and that of the police.
提出你和警方違法的證據
You'll face charges of false accusation, perjury,
除了犯下虛假指控罪和偽證罪以外
and fraud if you accept settlement money,
若接受和解金還會加上詐欺罪
with a prison sentence of up to ten years.
還會被處以十年以下的有期徒刑
Even if you receive a suspended sentence,
即使判緩刑
this case is receiving much media attention.
此案受到媒體的矚目
If it becomes known that a victim lied, you'll become their prime target.
而且被害者說謊 更是絕佳的炒作題材
Your face and name will remain online,
你的臉和名字將成為數位刺青
leaving a digital footprint that will stay with you forever.
在網路上留存一輩子
This will make it difficult to find a new job.
要找新工作會很困難吧
Even if you find someone you love,
就算你之後有喜歡的人
they'll eventually learn about this.
這件事被對方得知也只是時間問題
I wasn't lying.
我才沒有說謊
Listen,
不好意思
this is just one potential future that can still be changed.
我只是在說還可以改變的未來
You might as well finish your order.
既然來了，就慢慢享用吧
It's quite delicious.
很好吃喔
How did I do?
我的表現還行吧？
Splendidly.
你做得很好
The photo?
照片呢？
I sent it.
傳給她了
Now, it's in Ms. Shinomiya's hands
之後就看紫之宮小姐 要怎麼面對父親了
Welcome back.
你回來啦
Sorry, I only have random stuff.
沒什麼好東西可以招待你，抱歉啊
Will tea do?
喝茶可以嗎？
Sure.
可以
Here's Asuka. She's turned eight years old.
這是剛滿八歲的飛鳥
What do you want to be when you grow up?
長大後想要當什麼？
Um…
這個嘛…
a police officer!
警察！
Yeah!
好！
When was the last time you've been here?
你上次回來這裡是什麼時候？
The day I graduated from university.
大學畢業那天
It's been that long, huh?
過這麼久了啊？
I haven't come here since I became an attorney.
因為我當上律師後一次也沒回來過
What did you want to talk about?
你想談的是什麼？
You actually don't want to talk,
其實你不是想聊
you want to ask me something.
而是想問吧？
About Mr. Akizumi.
你想問明墨律師的事吧？
Does he know…
他知道我們的關係嗎？
He invited me to his office knowing all along.
他就是知道才邀我進事務所
This string of rape cases…
這次的不同意性交事件…
You know why Mr. Akizumi took over the defense for it, right?
你明白他為何要搶下辯護工作吧？
Mr. Akizumi suspects the third incident involving Ms. Eri Sendo was fabricated.
他懷疑第三起仙道繪里小姐案 是假造的事件
He thinks too little of the police.
他太小看警察了
If he brings that up in court,
要是他在法庭上如此主張
he'll be the one facing public backlash.
被輿論攻擊的會是明墨
Not if we've got evidence.
如果有證據就不一樣了吧？
There's no way there's any evidence.
怎麼可能有證據
Are you here to rattle me on Akizumi's orders?
是明墨派你來，好讓我動搖嗎？
You never know what might become proof.
因為不知道什麼會成為證據
So, an attorney should always record conversations.
律師要經常錄下對話
That's what Mr. Akizumi taught me.
明墨律師是這麼教我的
But…
不過…
it makes me careful with my words.
要是有這個，我說話也會有所顧慮
RECORDING
（錄音中）
RECORDING PAUSED
（暫停錄音）
I've always looked up to you.
我一直都很尊敬爸爸
But now, I'm not so sure…
但那樣是正確的嗎？
if I was right.
我現在已經搞不懂了
The Itoi family murders 12 years ago.
12年前的糸井家滅門案
It was after that incident…
自從那個事件後
that you stopped smiling.
你就失去笑容了
I was there.
我看到了
The day I graduated from university,
在大學畢業那天
Mr. Akizumi was pushing you for answers about that incident.
明墨律師來逼問你那個事件的詳情
You…
爸爸
covered something up about the Itoi family murders.
你在糸井家滅門案中掩蓋了某件事
You've been regretting it ever since, right?
從此一直活在後悔之中吧？
Tell me.
告訴我
Are you still the hero of justice…
你現在還是我所崇拜的…
whom I looked up to?
正義英雄嗎？
Please.
拜託你
Tell me.
告訴我吧
Is Mr. Yusaku Shimizu behind bars due to a false accusation?
志水裕策先生是因冤罪被捕嗎？
What did you do?
你又做了什麼？
Working under an eccentric attorney
在奇怪的律師手下工作
warps even your perspective, doesn't it?
連思考方式都會變得扭曲啊
The police work
所有的警察
tirelessly day and night to ensure citizens can live in peace.
為了讓市民安心生活 而不分晝夜持續努力
A false accusation?
冤罪？
Cover up?
掩蓋？
Absurd.
都是無稽之談
You're terribly mistaken.
是你自己搞錯了
Fine.
那就算了
We'll reveal the truth in the courtroom.
讓真相在法庭水落石出吧
We do have evidence.
我們有證據
Sorry. I just got concerned.
抱歉，因為我很在意
You were here the whole time?
你一直在這裡等我？
I've got a ton of work to catch up on, so Ms. Shiraki will be mad at me.
我還有很多工作沒做 一定會被白木小姐罵
It's hard, isn't it?
居然要欺騙父親
Lying to a parent.
你一定很難受吧？
I've been prepared for this
我從一開始
from the beginning.
就做好覺悟了
I'm fine.
我沒事的
Do you want a donut?
你要吃甜甜圈嗎？
No, thank you.
不用了
Wait, so you're not into sweets?
你是討厭甜食嗎？
How about salty stuff?
比較喜歡鹹的？
I prefer salty foods.
我比較喜歡鹹的
Salty, huh?
原來愛吃鹹的啊
Will this upset the balance?
真的能破壞平衡嗎？
Thanks to both of you, a crack has formed among the three.
多虧了你們，三者之間出現裂痕了
People carrying guilt in their hearts
越是心中有愧的人
are bound to feel increasingly anxious.
越會感到不安
The number you are trying to call is currently unreachable.
您所撥的電話無人接聽
ATTORNEY UNO
（宇野律師）
Excuse me.
打擾了
We've rechecked the security cameras at the station and the surrounding area,
我們徹底調查了車站和附近的監視器
but found nothing to contradict the testimony.
但沒有可以推翻證詞的畫面
Just as we initially thought, this case should be airtight.
這次的事件一如當初的預想 應該沒有缺失
As we suspected, Akizumi's goal is to shake us up.
明墨的目的果然是要讓我們動搖
Don't let it get to you.
不用在意
Right…
好的
Kurusu has a history of sexual offenses.
來栖重複犯下性犯罪
He deserves to be punished.
他該接受制裁
Um, are you sure everything is okay?
那個，真的沒問題嗎？
Can you avoid contacting me unless necessary?
你可以避免不必要的聯絡嗎？
-But-- -If something comes up, I'll call you.
-但是… -有什麼事情我會打給你
Don't worry.
不用擔心
You are a victim.
你有受害
That's why we took action and arrested Kurusu.
所以我們負起責任逮捕了來栖
Put your mind at rest.
請你安心度日
But…
不過…
Excuse me.
再見
CHIEF PROSECUTOR DATEHARA
（伊達原檢事正）
This is Kurata.
我是倉田
Oops, my bad.
抱歉，不好意思啊
It seems I called you by mistake.
我好像打錯了
No worries.
沒關係
But since I have you on the phone, I might as well ask.
不過既然打錯了，就順便問問吧
Everything's good, right?
你沒問題吧？
Yes.
當然
There are no issues at all.
沒有任何問題
I'm glad to hear that.
那就好
Um, it seems Akizumi is looking into that incident from 12 years ago.
那個，明墨果然 在追查12年前的那個事件
That incident?
“那個事件”？
What do you mean?
你是指什麼？
By the way,
啊，對了
your daughter's become an attorney, huh?
聽說你女兒當上了律師
I heard she's working at Akizumi Law Office now.
現在還在明墨法律事務所工作
Parents always want what they think is best for their kids,
不管父母多麼為孩子著想
but kids just can't help but rebel, can they?
孩子都會想要反抗呢
Anyway, you wouldn't want your dear daughter…
不過呢
to witness you in a sorry state, would you?
看到父親
So, that woman was lying?
意思是那女人說了謊？
Seems like she's got some serious resentment toward you.
她好像很恨你
Screw her!
別開玩笑了！
First, she pestered me relentlessly, and now this?
她一直糾纏我，最後還來這招！
"You were only good for your looks."
她可能是認為
Maybe she came to that conclusion.
你只不過是個長相好看的男人
Huh?
啥？
Are you looking for a fight?
你想吵架嗎？
Not at all.
不
You're going to expose her lies, right?
你會揭穿這個女人的謊言吧？
Yes.
我會的
Then, the first two cases--
那麼一開始的兩起事件也…
Mr. Kurusu.
來栖先生
You confessed to those
一開始的兩起事件是前任律師 逼迫你自白的吧？
But now, I'm the one on your defense.
現在的辯護律師是我
All right.
明白了
Well then.
那麼…
Ms. Sendo.
仙道小姐
I was asked to give this to you.
有人請我轉交這個
I had no clue you knew that hottie.
你跟那個帥哥認識啊？
Hottie?
帥哥？
Excuse me.
不好意思
What should I do about this person's exit record?
關於這個人的退館紀錄 該如何處理才好？
-Just a minute. -Yes.
你等一下
These are?
這些是什麼？
No idea.
我怎麼知道
These were sent to my workplace by that attorney!
是那個律師送到我公司的！
That attorney?
哪個律師？
Do you mean Akizumi?
明墨嗎？
Forcing me to see pictures of Kurusu with other women…
他還特地給我看 來栖和其他女人在一起的照片
Do I have to endure this harassment forever?
我得一生都受到這種騷擾嗎？
They're trying to mess with your head.
對方的目的是將你逼到精神崩潰
Once we win the trial, it'll all stop.
只要打贏官司，一切都會結束
Fine. In that case…
我知道了，那麼…
Can we use this in the trial?
這可以用在法庭上嗎？
VOICE MEMO
（語音備忘錄）
COURTHOUSE
（法院）
Next, we're moving on
那麼接著是檢方要求的證人訊問
Prosecutor, please get ready.
請檢方準備
Right.
-好的，就麻煩你了 -好
Um…
那個…
I don't need the partitions.
我不需要那個擋板
I want to handle this fair and square.
我想光明正大地與他對峙
Well then, prosecutor, you may begin.
那麼請檢察官訊問
In terms of privacy protection,
基於保護隱私的觀點
we sometimes keep the victim's name confidential.
有些案件不公布被害者名字
However, in this instance, we have the victim's consent.
但該案已經取得被害者的同意
Could you please state your name?
可以請問你的名字嗎？
I'm Eri Sendo.
仙道繪里
As outlined in the indictment,
如起訴狀所記載的
on February 21st, in Chiba Prefecture…
你在2月21日，於千葉縣…
Are you feeling unwell?
你不舒服嗎？
I'm okay.
我沒事
I'm just…
只是…
terrified.
覺得很可怕
Is it because the accused is so close?
是因為被告人在附近嗎？
No.
不是
The attorney…
因為辯護律師
questioned me relentlessly.
之前逼問過我
This is what you mentioned before the trial.
是你開庭前所說的事情吧？
That's right.
是的
Your Honor,
庭上
we've discovered that the defense contacted the victim
其實在不久前發現 辯護方接觸了被害者
and was using intimidation tactics.
並出言威脅
Could you clarify?
什麼意思？
I've obtained an audio recording from her
我收到她錄下的錄音
and I request an investigation into this evidence.
在此聲請調查證據
Defense counsel,
辯護人
I won't let you get away by pleading ignorance.
別說你不記得了
You wouldn't object to this, would you?
你不會反對吧？
In that case, can we use this in the trial?
那麼這可以用在法庭上嗎？
I was intimidated.
我被威脅了
In upcoming trials,
我們今後會在法庭上
we'll bring forth evidence of your dishonesty and that of the police.
提出你和警方違法的證據
You'll face charges of false accusation, perjury,
除了犯下虛假指控罪和偽證罪以外
and fraud if you accept settlement money,
若接受和解金還會加上詐欺罪
with a prison sentence of up to ten years.
還會被處以十年以下的有期徒刑
I did.
-將成為數位刺青… -是的
…that will stay with you forever.
在網路上留存一輩子
Even if you find someone you love,
就算你之後有喜歡的人
they'll eventually learn about this.
這件事被對方得知也只是時間問題
That wraps up the recording.
以上為證據
Based on this, I'd like to continue the questioning. May I?
可以根據這項證據再次開始訊問嗎？
You may continue.
請繼續
Witness,
請教一下證人
is this the voice of Attorney Akamine, seated over there?
這是坐在那邊的赤峰律師的聲音吧？
Yes, it is.
是的
Not only did the defense reach out to the victim,
辯護人不只是接觸被害者
and tried to get her to retract her testimony.
逼迫對方撤回證詞
They pressured you to distort the truth.
他們逼你扭曲事實
Is that correct?
對吧？
Witness?
證人
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
Are you feeling unwell?
你不舒服嗎？
If there's anything--
如果你還有其他…
That's not true.
不是這樣的
It wasn't intimidation.
我沒有被威脅
I begged Attorney Akamine to give me advice.
是我硬要找赤峰律師商量
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
I have something to share about the evidence you were interested in.
關於你想要知道的證據 我有話跟你說
What exactly does this prove?
這能夠成為什麼證據？
It shows that Mr. Kurusu was acquainted with many women other than you.
來栖先生除了你以外 還和很多女性有來往
That's not what I came here for!
我不是來問你這個的！
At the time of your assault,
在你遭受被害的時間
Mr. Kurusu didn't have an alibi.
來栖先生沒有不在場證明
That's what you thought, right?
你是這麼想的吧？
Actually,
其實事件發生當下 有來栖先生的位置資訊紀錄
You're lying.
你滿口謊言
Kurusu said his phone was turned off.
來栖說他手機關機了
This woman had secretly placed a GPS tracker in Mr. Kurusu's bag
這個女性為了找出 來栖先生劈腿的對象
to find out who he was playing around with.
在來栖先生的包包裡
That can't be.
-不會吧 -我們要在法庭上揭露這項事實
You collaborated with the police to fabricate charges for a false incident.
你協助警方告發虛假的事件
This is totally a crime.
這是貨真價實的犯罪行為
However…
但是呢
If you were simply manipulated by the police…
如果你只是被警方利用
and had no choice but to cooperate in fabricating the incident,
逼不得已，只好幫忙假造事件
it's a different story.
那事情就不一樣了
You're a victim.
你會是被害者
A victim?
被害者？
Yes.
沒錯
If you admit that you were threatened by the police
只要坦白自己是被警方威脅
and still complied with them despite your conscience,
所以違背良心幫了他們
the blame will be directed at the police.
有罪的就是警方了
All you need to do is testify that you were intimidated.
你說出被威脅的證詞即可
You wanted to bring Mr. Kurusu down.
你想要陷害來栖先生
Isn't that right?
對吧？
We won't let him go unpunished.
我們不會放他自由
You have our word.
我向你保證
You have two options.
你現在有兩個選擇
If we present this evidence,
我們只要提出那個證據
you'll be seen as accomplices with the police.
你和警方就會變成共犯
You'll be arrested on charges of false accusation and perjury,
屆時會因虛假指控罪和偽證罪被逮捕
while Kurusu will go free.
另一邊，來栖則會被正式釋放
You can accept this outcome,
你想要那樣的未來嗎？
or you can cooperate with us.
還是要和我們合作
You can send Kurusu, who caused you pain, to hell.
把讓你痛苦的來栖推入地獄？
Do you want this outcome?
這是第二個未來
Consider very carefully.
請仔細考慮吧
What should I do?
我該怎麼做？
I…
我…
I hated Mr. Kurusu,
我因為怨恨來栖先生
and lied about him harming me.
而謊稱自己遭受被害
However,
不過…
after speaking with the attorneys,
聽了律師的話後
I've come to realize the gravity of the crime I've committed.
我察覺到自己犯下很大的過錯
No matter how much I hated him,
無論多麼恨一個人
it was thoughtless of me to be used for his unlawful arrest.
我竟被警方利用 違法逮捕對方，實在太膚淺了
I'm truly sorry.
真的萬分抱歉
Prosecutor.
檢方
What’s going on here?
這到底是什麼情況？
You accused even our quest for truth as intimidation
你們將我們對真相的追求說成是威脅
and tried to fabricate a crime out of thin air.
還想編造出不存在的犯罪
Well…
那是…
What are you looking at?
你在看什麼？
Nothing.
沒什麼
Surely, you won't suggest this was orchestrated by the police too.
你該不會想說這也是警方準備的吧？
Don't tell me you presented this recording without even verifying it.
你們該不會是沒做任何查證 就提出這錄音檔？
No, I--
不，所以說…
Never mind.
沒關係
The truth will come out.
接下來真相就會大白
Isn't that right,
對吧？
Chief Kurata?
倉田刑事部長
Order in the court.
肅靜
We will conclude today's trial.
本日的審理到此為止
We will review the situation
我們再次釐清狀況後
and decide how to proceed with future trials.
將決定之後的審理進行方式
Prosecutor and defense counsel,
檢方和辯護方請在閉庭後 立刻來法官辦公室
The court is adjourned.
退庭
How serious will my crime be?
我會被判多重的罪？
That depends on your attorney.
這就要看律師如何辯護了
Can I ask you to represent me?
可以拜託你嗎？
Relax.
請放心
We're partners, after all.
我們是合作關係
The GPS tracker in Kurusu's bag.
來栖的包包被放了定位系統追蹤器
You lied about it, right?
那是騙人的吧？
Maybe.
你覺得呢？
It doesn't matter.
是真是假都沒關係
You'll handle Kurusu, won't you?
你會好好懲罰來栖吧？
I will.
當然會
You even expected Ms. Eri to see through it?
繪里小姐會發現 也在你的預料之中嗎？
Perhaps.
天曉得
Kurusu is actually guilty of the first and second cases, right?
來栖在第一、第二起事件中 真的有犯罪吧？
What will you do next?
之後你要怎麼做？
Good grief!
真是的
The police are such a disappointment.
警方真是讓人無言以對！
They can't make an arrest without inventing evidence!
不捏造證據就不能逮捕犯人嗎？
My bad.
抱歉…
I've been complaining a lot lately.
我最近變得很愛抱怨
Maybe it's my old age.
是不是因為上了年紀啊？
Come to think of it,
話說回來…
your ex-husband is a UTokyo graduate and a police official, right?
我記得你的前夫
Yes.
是的
Could I ask you a little favor?
可以幫我一個忙嗎？
So, Mr. Yashiro,
也就是說第三起事件 是警方捏造的虛構案件
This is quite unprecedented.
這種事真的前所未聞
The police fabricating an incident is utterly disgraceful behavior.
警方竟然假造事件，真是醜態盡出
What about the woman who testified she was threatened by the police?
女性供出自己是被警方威脅的
What will happen to her?
她會怎麼樣呢？
If the police coerced her testimony through intimidation,
如果是警方逼迫她做出偽證
she shouldn't be charged with a serious crime.
應該不會被判很重的罪
Ms. Eri will face a difficult time after this.
繪里小姐接下來也會很辛苦吧
Um…
那個…
Were you in on everything, Mr. Aoyama?
青山先生其實全都知道嗎？
Who knows?
你說呢？
It's time.
時間到了喔
Attorney Akizumi, please go ahead.
那麼請明墨律師發言
The police's unlawful conduct in this case was incredibly sloppy
這次警方所做的違法行為 實在太過草率了
and undermines Japan's justice system.
完全在愚弄日本的司法
As an attorney,
這是我身為一個律師的意見
I feel it's crucial to investigate past cases as well.
我認為過去的事件應該也要追查
On the other hand,
另一方面
I uncovered something while defending this case.
在擔任此次事件的辯護工作時
Mr. Kurusu, my client,
雖然來栖先生是我的委託人
was also found to be making a false claim.
但我發現他的主張造假
I believe an attorney should act as a guardian for their client,
雖然我認為律師要保護委託人
but I must stick to my principles.
不過我基於自身的信念
Therefore,
就在剛才辭去了來栖先生的律師職務
I'd like to hand the case back to Attorney Uno,
我想將這個職務還給讓委託人自白
who led the client to confess and encouraged him to repent.
使其發自內心反省的宇野律師
Daddy, what's wrong?
爸爸，你怎麼了？
Nothing.
沒事
Daddy will work hard for you, Yua.
爸爸會為了夢愛拼命工作的
He's handing the case back to Attorney Uno?
還給宇野律師沒問題嗎？
He'll have to make a fresh start for the sake of his wife and daughter.
他為了老婆和女兒也只能改過自新吧
Well then…
接下來…
Are you moving?
你要搬家嗎？
I'll be investigated internally.
我會在警局內接受調查
I'll either face disciplinary action
看是被免除職務
or be kept on the payroll with no real work.
還是得到冗職
Either way, I can't continue living here anymore.
不管是哪一個 都無法繼續住在這裡了
Asuka…
飛鳥
Dad.
爸爸
In this case, First Investigation Division Chief Onishi
在本案，搜查一課的大西課長 被迫負起責任辭職
Were you trying to protect him by any chance?
爸爸，你該不會是 為了保護那個人而行動吧？
Were you protecting something back then too?
你當時也是為了保護什麼嗎？
Answer me, Mr. Kurata.
請告訴我，倉田先生
You unlawfully covered that up, didn't you?
你是不是用不正當手段 掩蓋了那件事？
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼
Please leave.
請回吧
What are you trying to protect even at the cost of breaking the law?
你不惜犯法也要保護的到底是什麼？
I just…
我只是希望…
want you to smile like you used to.
你能像以前一樣開心地笑著
Asuka…
飛鳥
I'm sorry.
對不起
Mr. Kurata, you're home, aren't you?
倉田先生，你在家吧？
It's the police.
我們是警察
Please open the door.
請開門
You're Mr. Isao Kurata, correct?
你是倉田功先生吧？
This is the Chiba Police Second Investigation Division.
我們是千葉縣警搜查二課
We have an arrest warrant for you
我們要以幫助虛假指控 以及違反國家公務員法的嫌疑逮捕你
We will take you to the department.
我們會將你帶到警局 法院也給了搜索扣押令
and other officials will conduct a search of your home.
現在開始其他職員會搜索你家
Right.
知道了
Asuka…
飛鳥
Forget about me.
忘了我吧
Wait.
等一下
Wait, Dad!
別走啊，爸爸！
Dad!
爸爸！
I see.
明白了
Thank you.
謝謝
Sorry.
抱歉啊
He might have been silenced.
可能是為了封口
What do you mean?
這是怎麼一回事？
Was his arrest unlawful too?
逮捕他也是違法行為？
No.
不
They acted awfully quickly,
雖然他們的動作很快
but there was nothing unlawful about Kurata's arrest.
但是關於倉田的逮捕 警方沒有任何不當
I suppose not…
我想也是
So…
接下來…
what should I do now?
我該怎麼辦？
You can either continue to see him as your father,
對於犯了罪的人
despite his crime…
仍然要把他當成父親
or reject him.
還是要捨棄他
The choice is yours.
那是你的自由
You have a clear mind of your own.
你有明確的意志
Act on it.
只要實行即可
Both as an attorney
作為一個律師
and as a daughter.
作為一個女兒
Thank you.
謝謝你
Take care and come back.
路上小心，我等你回來
Sorry to keep you waiting.
讓你久等了
He just went in.
他剛剛進去了
I believe he went to see Akizumi.
應該是去找明墨
Is that so?
這樣啊
I suspected as much.
果然如此
So, it's connected to that incident.
他果然和那個事件有關啊
So…
所以…
Can you get your hands on that thing?
你有辦法拿到那個東西嗎？
Yes.
有
Well then…
那麼…
shall we begin?
差不多該開始了吧
Subtitle translation by: Ai Matsuoka
字幕翻譯：洪禎韓
Maybe Mr. Akizumi got an acquittal for Hiyama for a reason.
明墨律師幫助緋山獲判無罪 該不會也是有理由的吧
The evidence speaks for itself.
證據說明了一切 就像在催人快進行逮捕
She's maintaining her innocence, insisting she was framed by someone.
她主張自己無罪 說是被其他人陷害的
If all these cases are connected…
如果至今的案件也全都有關連…
I want to uncover what my father is hiding too.
我也想知道父親到底在隱瞞什麼
Please join me in this fight again.
請再跟我一同並肩作戰
I've been eagerly awaiting you.
恭候多時了
None of the evidence was accepted?
所有證據都沒被採用？
This made their connection clear.
這麼一來那些傢伙的關係 就變得十分清楚
Now that I know, I can't back down.
既然都知道了，我就無法退讓
You anticipated this, didn't you?
明墨律師早已預料到了吧？
Akizumi is relentless.
明墨很頑強
Don't let him catch you out.
小心不要被他抓到把柄
I'll expose their corruption.
我會揭露那傢伙的黑暗面